<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TEMPLATE</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on TEMPLATE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>01: intro</title><link>/week1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week1/</guid><description>we&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 course intro 6841 week01 &amp;gt; whoami Lachlan TODO: more stuff here how to contact me lachlan.waugh@student.unsw.edu.au @melon on the SecEdu Slack @melon on the SecSoc Discord places for course discussion discord.gg/TODO
~/security/ &amp;gt; comp6441-6841 seceduau.slack.com/signup
#cs6441 &amp;gt; whoru what&amp;rsquo;s your name/degree? why did you decide to do this course? what&amp;rsquo;s your favourite course you&amp;rsquo;ve done, and why? OpenLearning walkthrough (wow!) join the H18B-6841 Tutorial Group (if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already) change your profile picture to a picture of yourself (or don&amp;rsquo;t) Good faith policy we expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses.</description></item><item><title>02: sqli</title><link>/week2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week2/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 sqli 6841 week02 housekeeping class notes our tutorial is scheduled to do the lecture notes for the wednesday lecture of week 4
class representatives you get to attend meetings with Richard?
have they mentioned this? if you want to nominate yourself, cool maybe we can vote as a class? logbooks feedback on logbooks some didn&amp;rsquo;t do the learning community/dealing with challenges sections. this is worth 40% of the mark per week, you should do it.</description></item><item><title>03: xss</title><link>/week3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week3/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 cross-site scripting 6441 Week03 good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
tldr: don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick jerk
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
housekeeping logbooks Summary 👎 &amp;ldquo;short, concise, and comprehensive version of a longer original work.&amp;rdquo; Analysis 👍 &amp;ldquo;a breakdown of the examination and evaluation of an original document or text.</description></item><item><title>04: overflows</title><link>/week4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week4/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 buffer overflows 6441 week04 good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
tldr: don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick jerk
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
housekeeping something awesome would anyone like to discuss their progress
secedu conference there&amp;rsquo;s a secedu conference in week 6 $20 admission for students?</description></item><item><title>07: ctf</title><link>/week7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week7/</guid><description>we&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 ctf, rootkits &amp;amp;&amp;amp; more 6441 week07 good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
tldr: don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick jerk
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
housekeeping revision cryptographic hash function w/ a 60 bit hash, on average 20 bits of work to hash a short document On average how many bits of work would it take to find two short documents with the same hash</description></item><item><title>8: re</title><link>/week8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week8/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 reverse engineering 6441 week8 good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
tldr: don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick jerk
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
housekeeping reverse engineering the process of deconstructing a program to work out it&amp;rsquo;s underlying code, architecture, design, etc
essentially getting the source code of an application, without being given it what types of reverse engineering are there?</description></item><item><title>re</title><link>/re/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/re/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 Reverse Engineering 6841 Lecture 7? good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
do this irl its cool
topics req knowledge static analysis dynamic analysis deobfuscation required knowledge static analysis disassembling
dynamic analysis debugging
deobfuscation degarbage
questions?</description></item><item><title>Week05</title><link>/week5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week5/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll get started at 18:05 format strings 6441 Week05 good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
tldr: don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick jerk
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
housekeeping make sure you&amp;rsquo;re doing the extended challenges buffer overflows, format strings, xss, sqli
questions public/private keys if 10 people wanted to communicate privately (one-on-one), how many:</description></item></channel></rss>